Hi.
Hey, guys. Thank you for joining. I can
see a few of you have been in the waiting
room. Thank you for coming in early. I was
thinking just, you know, well, first of
all, let me know in the chat if you don't
mind, if you can see me, if you can see
the screen, if you can hear me, just
confirm that everything is okay, say hi or
let me know if everything is working
correctly. And by the way, I... Perfect.
Thank you so much, Omer. I know that we're
supposed to start right now, but I was
thinking to give maybe a minute or two for
other people to join. So while we're
waiting, I guess you can let me know if
you guys have some experience. Have you
worked with brokerages before? Have you...
Were you an affiliate, an IB? Did you have
your own brokerage in the past? Or did you
just kind of consider starting your own
brokerage? Not sure where to start? Which
regions to target?
Let me know. And let me just check the
couple of things on my side as well.
Okay. Looking good. Oh, nice. I see. I
see. More people are joining. That's good
to see. And I don't know how familiar you
are, you know, with QuadCode. Have you
heard of us before? Is this kind of your
first introduction? I guess you can see on
screen. I think we kind of... We can start
with the introductions as people solely
join as well. For us, we have been on the
market, you know, building brokerages for
12 years now. And we have built over 50
brokerages. I think at this point, it's
even closer to 60. But yeah, let's keep it
conservative. And we are a huge
organization with over 700 employees. And
we have covered so far 169 countries. And
that kind of gives us, we feel, pretty
solid experience, you know, kind of an
idea of how the markets work, and what's
working best. So it's not that we're just
running a brokerage in one country or in
one region. No, we're truly global. So we
kind of have the evidence of what's
working in which region, because they are
different. And you will see that, by the
way, you will see that in our, in the
presentation, we have found, like, there
are some discrepancies, which are going to
affect when you start to launch a
brokerage, whether with us or alone. These
decisions need to be made, and you need to
make them very carefully. Okay, I think, I
think we're good to go. It's been three
minutes. So yeah, that's a little bit
about us. Now, let's move on. Yeah, there
it is, the next slide. So first of all,
let's just really quickly cover the
background question for all of this, which
is, is the brokerage business dead in
2026? Soon to be 2027, I guess. Our answer
is definitely not. So we at Quadcode, we
have been building businesses, and we have
been in this business on the other side,
you know, running a brokerage for a long
time. And if anything, we're busier than
ever. So the demand is real, and the
opportunity is real. And the brokerages
that we've helped build, so over 50,
again, closer to 60 at this point, they
are a proof of that. Our clients typically
see a return on investment within just
three months, which I'm sure if you've
started any business, you know, that's
kind of a dream come true, almost unheard
of. And so today, rather than debating,
you know, whether it even makes sense,
let's discuss on, you know, where it makes
sense, what's going to work best for you.
Again, whether you do this with us or do
it alone. So first of all, what, what
steps will you need to cover? What needs
to happen for you to have a brokerage?
Number one, you need to set up a platform
and decide, you know, how you want to
design it. What do you want to include?
What do you want to offer to your clients,
to the traders themselves? Then you need
to choose the markets. And again, the
instruments that you're going to offer,
this is going to heavily depend on the
markets that you decide to target. You
need to understand the regulations. And
this is also going to be decided by the,
by the regions that you select. You need
to form a legal entity, so the right
structure for your region. You need to
plan trader acquisition strategy. So how
are you going to get clients on the
platform? And more than that, once you get
them on the platform, how are you going to
incentivize them to start trading? You
need to connect payment gateways, so you
can actually accept money. Again, this is
going to heavily depend on the, on the
geography that you're targeting. And then
you will need to integrate all of that
software and set up your CRM. And then
you're ready to launch essentially. So,
and this is, by the way, whether you go
with us or you do this alone, that's the
process is going to be pretty much the
same. So what you've heard in this list
earlier, I mentioned, this is going to
depend on geography, this is going to
depend on the region, this is going to
depend on the market. What all of that
means is that it's really, truly,
incredibly important where, what, what,
again, what locale, what region you want
to target. And what a lot of new brokers
do is they, well, they just think that
they need to target the region where they
are from. So we need to spend a minute on
that because we've done quite a bit of
research on it. And the numbers show
something different. So after screening
worldwide markets, these five came out on
top, Brazil, Indonesia, Colombia, Nigeria,
and Philippines. All of these five,
they're excellent markets to target, and
you will want to consider them, consider
opening there. However, what the numbers
92, 88, 80, 76, 72, what this is telling
you is the order. So if we're looking at
the spread, Brazil at 92, Philippines at
72, that's a 20 point gap between the top
and bottom of the list. And this should
point you to the priority, to this is
essentially a priority list. So if someone
tells you, oh, just launch everywhere, or
just launch in your home country, this
list points to why that actually doesn't
work. And let's dive a bit deeper into
specific reasons. And this is where it
gets interesting. So the red here, this is
the commercial opportunity. Essentially,
how much money is on the table? And then
gray is execution readiness. And then gray
is execution readiness. Meaning, how
quickly can you actually stand a brokerage
up in these regions? So Brazil and
Indonesia, they're tight. 92 against 84
and 88 against 82. Small gap, meaning
what's on the paper is close to what you
can actually execute. And these need to be
your step one markets. This is where you
want to start, especially again, when
you're new to this, you want to go for
what's tried and tested, you don't want to
start with a difficult market first, you
want to start where it's easier. And then
you want to go where, you know, there
might be higher risk, but higher
opportunity, essentially. Now, comparing
Nigeria and Philippines, Nigeria scores
higher on the opportunity for sure. It's
clear 76 against 72 points. But this is on
pure opportunity ranking. Nigeria would go
first. However, when we're looking at
readiness, it's 58 against 62. So Nigeria
has the widest gap on this whole chart. We
are looking at 18 points. In this gap,
this is payment. And that's, that's real
profit. That's real profit that you might
be missing out on. If, let's say you
select Nigeria as your number one market.
That's the issue. So Philippines, in this
case, needs to go ahead of Nigeria. And
even though Nigeria might have a bigger,
you know, upside on the paper, this is not
us being timid about it. We work there, we
have open brokerages there. It's on the
list. It's a, it's a good market that you
want to target. However, as I said
earlier, don't go to the hardest market
first. First, learn to learn your own,
learn your own operation. Start where it's
easier. Oh, Joe can't see the screen. Oh,
my goodness. I'm so sorry. I only now see
can, can other people see the screen? Oh,
my goodness. I hope I haven't been talking
and not showing you anything.
Oh, okay. Oh, you can see. Sorry about
that. I was so I was looking at the
numbers. I didn't even see the message.
Sorry. Okay, good. You can see it. All
right. So coming back to it. It's
important to understand what's the
difference between opportunity and
execution. Next slide is going to show us
how to then put all of this information
together. And how that is going to inform
your next steps. Again, whether you're
doing this with us, or you're building a
brokerage on your own, this is important
information to have. This, again, you need
to take this into consideration. So
putting it all together, your step one, or
wave one needs to be or should be Brazil
Indonesia. That's where you can launch,
prove your model, learn your funnel with
the least amount of friction. That's where
it's going to be the easiest. That's where
you're, again, that's where you can learn
to walk before you run. Step number two,
that should be Colombia and the
Philippines. So now you're scaling demand
and you're localizing more deeply. And
then step number three, that's going to be
Nigeria. You're going with tighter risk
and compliance controls for sure. But then
you've got two previous steps of operating
history behind you. You've got experience,
and you've still got those people on your
platform, knowing how well, you know, how
well it works. And hopefully, you know, as
you expand, as you grow, as your profits
increase, you're able to offer more and
more and more to them. So they're going to
stay loyal customers as then you proceed
further, and you can offer more to even
the Nigerian market. So then they have a
larger incentive to actually execute on
the opportunity that we discussed before.
Now, you see underneath it, the five
drivers that define geo readiness. This
is, this is essentially what's going to
decide if a market is ready for you. So
it's going to be a regulation, payments,
acquisition, local fit, and retention. And
this is the line you should really, you
know, keep in mind when it comes to when
it comes to this whole point. Geo choice
only works when it connects to KYC, PSPs,
CRM, risks, reporting, apps, and
retention. So choosing Brazil is not going
to be a decision that you just, you know,
you spin the globe and put a put a finger
somewhere and it lands on Brazil. No,
this, this needs to be a decision whether
your KYC providers cover Brazilian
documents, whether your PSPs support
picks, the most popular PSP over there,
whether your CRM speaks Portuguese,
whether your support team is in your risk
team. Also, they are awake, and they also
speak Portuguese during their, you know,
in their time zone, all of this, you need
to take into consideration. So it's a,
it's a big decision. So it's important to
have all of the the information in front
of you, you know, when, before even you
start. Now, that's what I was mentioning
just now. Here's a breakdown of what we
do. And again, whether you decide to go
with us, or you want to build a brokerage
on your own, you're going to need all of
these. And you're going to need it
contextually, regarding the region where
you want to operate. So for us, all of the
brokerages that we built, we make sure
that they're ready to work out, you know,
right out of the box. In any case, what
you need, you need a dealing team, you
need risk management, they have to protect
you from market risk, industry, and just
bad actors who are trying to abuse the
platform. Like these are unavoidable. You
need a billing system. So Visa,
MasterCard, Apple Pay, Google Pay, crypto,
local payment methods. Most important of
all, local payment methods. I mean, this
is going to be such a huge headache. I
know because it is, it has been a headache
for us. I know how many hoops we had to
jump through to get recognized to get
approved in each country. So as you open
in different markets, expect that. Unless
you go with us, since we have had those
headaches for you. Then what else is going
to be analytics and reporting. This is not
just a requirement, but you also need to
understand what channels are working for
you and what needs more attention. And
then, especially when it comes to
reporting for us, we, in addition to, you
know, what we have built on our own, we
also pay a lot for a Metabase integration.
If you're familiar with Metabase, you
know, they are a behemoth in the industry,
and they are very powerful analytics tool
for business insights. So, in any case,
recommend them. If you can afford them,
highly recommend them. Liquidity.
Liquidity. For us, we have already
providers and data feed providers already
integrated. You're going to need
cybersecurity, you know, fraud protection,
system security, your KYC and compliance
reporting. I mean, this is just regulated
in every single country. And then CRM is a
huge one. You need a really good CRM that
is deeply, deeply integrated with your
platform. For us, because we know we have
gone through the hell and we know what it
looks like when it's, you know, when it's
a third party. You're going to spend
months integrating and then you're going
to spend another year fixing all of the
integration issues. And then still
something may fall through the cracks. So,
for us, we have built our own in-house CRM
that everything is covered right away. You
don't need to worry about anything. And
then, of course, all of this looks great
unless you have, you know, trade. So,
you're also an affiliate and omnichannel
modules. You know, these are essential for
growing your trader base and then also
managing retention. Because, again, it's
one thing to have people show up. It's a
different thing to have them start trading
and, you know, start putting their money
where their mouth is. And then, yeah, this
is just something that, you know, this is
the makeup on top of everything. So,
everything, this is what you can expect
from our platforms at least. We provide
more than 150 CFDs, more than 70
cryptocurrencies, and 24-7 support. And
also, we provide the web trading room,
Android, iOS apps, progressive web app,
and, of course, desktop. So, all of that
can be fully customized. Oh, my goodness.
I just realized we changed this. Okay. So,
that can be fully custom. Not going back.
Oh, no. Did my screen freeze? Oh, yeah. It
did. Okay. Perfect. So, all of that is
going to be fully customized. It's going
to be fully branded. Your logo, your
domain,
all of that. Yeah. Interface, logo,
colors, trading tools. Again, trading
tools, you'll want to adjust this for geo.
And also, you know your community. You
know your niche. That needs to also kind
of align. And then, numbers. Looking at
numbers, you can see our brokerages start
at $17,000. And you will hear, you will
definitely look, just go Google it. You'll
find people offering you a brokerage for
$10,000 and even $5,000. But those offers
usually cover only the basics.
The rest of the stack is charged
separately.
[Brief connection interruption]
Okay. Let's just pretend everything is
okay.
What these people are not telling you is
that you're going to pay extra
going to pay extra for a CRM, for the
dealing desk, for the PSPs. I can tell you
PSPs are also, I think I already
mentioned, they're going to be a huge
headache. You're going to need to get
liquidity providers. They're also going to
try to, you know, skin you alive. You're
going to need to figure out KYC and all of
the infrastructure that, you know, sits
behind that I mentioned previously. Okay.
So, looking at.
With us, everything you need is included.
It works right out of the box. Another
big upside, it takes us 14 days, two weeks
to launch this. And then what we've seen
in our experience, it's a three-month
payback period, which is, again, if you've
ever run a business before, that's a
pretty good payback period. Yes, this is
what I was mentioning. So, you can see,
for us, it's going to be $17,000.
Competitors will quote $5,000 or $10,000.
And then you're going to end
up overpaying, like, from $5 for every
million traded. Then you're going to get 2
,000 per month for the CRM. And these are
conservative numbers. This is not just us,
you know, pretending, oh, our competitors
are words. No, genuinely, this is what
you're going to hear. It's going to be
starting at $1,000 for PSPs. I promise
you, it's going to be way more. Liquidity,
I mean, set up minimum 3,000. All these
numbers, they're not coming out of thin
air. They're coming out of our experience.
In the end, it's going to cost you way
more than it is if you just take it as a
whole. Moving on. Oh, yeah. This is just a
few quotes from the traders who are on the
platforms that we have built, or the happy
customers of the happy customers. And then
here, you can essentially see what we're
trying to do at the end. Your success is
going to be our success. We want you to be
as profitable as humanly possible, ideally
from day one. So what do we do to help you
with that? We provide the full brokerage
launch checklist. And our team will go
with you through it all to make sure that
everything is
especially
useful. If you've got an IB or affiliate
background, you will know exactly what
this looks like, what this means. Business
plans and blog resources. And then we also
have a whole team who will be dedicated,
an entire team of account managers who are
going to be at your back-end call, making
sure, again, that your platform works
exactly as you want it to work and that it
is profitable. We're here to give you
advice. We're here to support you every
step of the way. For us, it's not just,
oh, here's a platform. You figure it out.
It's a long-term partnership.
And, yeah, these are just some of the next
steps that you can take. Essentially, what
I would like to do is invite you to a
demo. Come.
I'll explain exactly. I'll show you. Oh,
my goodness. Streaming connection lost
again. Is it? Am I? I hope I'm back
online. Oh, terrible, terrible luck. So
I'm inviting you to a one-on-one demo. I
will sit down with you. I would like to
hear more about your experience, hear more
about what you want to achieve, exactly
what kind of a brokerage you want to
build, help you understand, you know, what
we might be able to do, what path will
probably be the best for you to take. At
that point, if you do decide to go with
us, we're going to customize your platform
fully. So, again, the whole team asking
you, hey, what do you want to do about
this? And you'll just say, hey, I want to
do that. I want to do this. When it's
ready, you just sign the contract. The
platform goes live. And at that point, the
only thing that you need to worry about is
getting a connection loss again. Jesus.
We're going to help you when it comes to
the strategies. You know, what do you
need? What do you, should you, you know,
create attorneys? Do you need live chats?
Should you have challenges? Which, of
course, you should. And then we're going
to recommend what works best for your
region. So, yeah. If you would like to
chat with us, this is my personal
WhatsApp. You can just scan the code.
Message me. Let me know, you know,
whatever date, time works for you. We'll
arrange something. We will book a demo.
Again, just an informal conversation. See
what you would like to achieve and see if
we can help. By the way, I forgot to
mention this. I should have mentioned it
earlier on. If you guys have any
questions, you can feel free to drop them
in the chat or message me on WhatsApp,
whichever works best. More than happy to
answer anything, show you, give you access
again, give you access to the demo,
whatever that may be. And, yeah. Oh,
perfect. Yes. I see some of you are
already messaging me. Yes, we'll connect.
I think the webinar is coming to a close.
Technically, it's supposed to go on for
six more minutes. If there are no
questions, I think we can even end up with
earlier, give you some time back. But if
you do have any questions, I'll hang
around for a couple more minutes. Feel
free to send anything in the chat. Oh,
yeah. And one more thing. Because we are
international, we have, as I mentioned, an
international team. If you don't speak
English, well, I don't know if you would
understand me. But if you don't speak
English or a friend of yours who wants to
start a brokerage doesn't speak English,
feel free to still reach out. Again, we
have a lot of translators, a huge team. We
can find a way to communicate. Yeah. I
think that's fair enough. Reach out to us.
Reach out to me. Feel free to let me know,
you know, whatever, whenever you would
like to start. Whatever questions you may
have, and so on. Thank you so much for
spending the time with me. And, yeah, hope
to see you soon. Bye, guys.